okay so I wanted to update that I'm no
longer doing a daily video on this
channel what may be happening is more
than a daily video and days in between
without one what I am committed to doing
on this channel is hosting the QA live
at 11 a.m. on Fridays Pacific Standard
Time then when I feel a need to answer a
question that was generated basically
anywhere on social media I will come and
do a video with that question explaining
it so that's will be me Solo in videos
explaining the question about global
cooperative or me responding to
something that I saw on YouTube that I
feel the need to speak out into the
universe in video format what I do want
to do on this channel is find more
people to have a conversation with like
I did with Clara yesterday and put up
more of that because I enjoy being part
of those discussions and it helps me
hone the idea it introduces other people
to other people's ideas I that will be
what I am focusing on also I'm gonna be
focusing on doing a somewhat daily video
on the idea cafe the new channel that is
the one timeslot 11:00 a.m. on
Wednesdays
Pacific Standard Time and where we I
gather a group of people to answer a
question live and they just have to show
up as themselves and share what is in
their heart in that moment but I'm also
going to be doing a daily video they're
reaching out to YouTube youtubers that
have more
influence and asking them to come be a
part of it and asking them to bring
their communities with them so asking
them to pick a question pick a time
period that we can host that won't be
live but then those will be will be
uploaded right now I'm really excited I
want to reach out to Chris from SBS Kay
because I love his videos and so that is
what the video I'm going to do today on
idea cafe this was going to be a video
on the sharing economy I was gonna
answer a question but I think this will
be two different videos hence the more
than one video a day which I felt like I
was limiting myself and pushing it
forward too much on the days when I
would just come on and be like well I
gotta do a video today and that's
exactly what I needed in the moment but
now that I've come across game B and
that community and now that the idea
cafe has started I feel like my focus
needs to be elsewhere from forcing
myself to do daily videos so that is
what this update is is what this channel
is is evolving into and I will be back
on what they'll be doing today I guess I
can't see I'll see you tomorrow
but a better world is on its way it's
gonna be brought to you by our diversity
and you get to watch it unfold
maybe not live on YouTube but definitely
on YouTube as long as they don't kick me
off take care